displayninja.com 2019-12-20

# Privacy Policy | DisplayNinja

**Effective Date: June 12, 2019**

This Privacy Policy describes the types of information that Flexter ApS (“Flexter”, “we”, “us” or “our”) collects from and about you when you visit our website, displayninja.com (“Site”). This Privacy Policy also describes how we may use and disclose such information, as well as your ability to control certain uses of it.

By browsing and using the site, you agree to the collection, use, and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. You also agree to our Terms of Use, which are incorporated by reference. If you do not agree, please do not access or use the site.

## Personal Information That We Collect

### Information You Provide

We collect personal information from you when you choose to share it with us.  This may include when you use our Site, sign up for newsletters or our email list, use our service, leave a comment, enter into giveaways or other promotions, fill out a survey, request support or information from us, subscribe to our web push notifications, or otherwise communicate with or contact us.  The personal information we collect may include your name, address, email address, telephone or mobile number, date of birth, and gender.

 **Information You Provide Through Social Media**

You may also be given the option to link to your Facebook or another social media account through the Site. When you do, we may automatically receive certain information about you based on your registration and privacy settings on those third party services. This may include, but may not be limited to, name, user name, demographic information, updated address or contact information, location, interests, and publicly-observed data, such as from social media and online activity.

### Information Automatically Collected

We may use a variety of technologies such as cookies, pixel tags, log files, or other technologies to collect certain information about visitors to, and users of, our Site and interactions with our emails and online advertisements, and to allow us to keep track of analytics and certain statistical information

For example, we may automatically collect certain non-personal information from you, including but not limited to your browser type, device type, operating system, carrier information, unique device identifier of any of your computer(s) or device(s) that are used to access the Site, software version, Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, geolocation, phone model, phone operating system, and the domain name from which you accessed the Site.  We also may collect information about your use of the Site, including the date and time you visit the Site, the areas or pages of the Site that you visit, the amount of time you spend viewing or using the Site, the number of times you return to the Site, other click-stream or site usage data, emails that you open, forward or click-through to our Site, and other sites that you may visit.

 **Third Party Service Providers**

We may use third-party service providers to support our Site.  Some of these service providers may use technology such as cookies, web beacons, pixel tags, log files or other technologies to receive, collect, and store information.

 **Geni.us Geotargeting Technology**

We may use geni.us link technology for some of our links. They will redirect you to the most appropriate Amazon storefront based on your public IP.

Links starting with geni.us are smart geni.us links. Links to Amazon.com may also be subject to Geni.us Geotargeting Technology when clicked on.

Read their privacy policy [here](https://www.geni.us/privacy).

 **Third Party Analytic Technologies**

We may use third parties’ analytics and tracking tools to better understand who is using the Site, how people are using the Site, how to improve the effectiveness of the Site and related content and to help us or those third parties serve more targeted advertising to you across the Internet. These tools may use technology such as cookies, web beacons, pixel tags, log files, or other technologies to collect and store non-personal information. They may also combine information they collect from your interaction with the Site with information they collect from other sources. We do not have access to, or control over, these third parties’ use of cookies or other tracking technologies.

### Information Collected From Other Sources

We may acquire information from other trusted sources to update or supplement the information that you provide or that we collect automatically (such as information to validate or update your address or other demographic and lifestyle information). We may use this information to help us maintain the accuracy of the information we collect, to target our communications so that we can inform you of products, services or other offers that may be of interest to you, and for internal business analysis or other business purposes.

### Combination of Information

We may combine the information we receive from and about you, including information you provide to us and information we automatically collect through our Site, as well as information collected offline, across other computers or devices that you may use, and from third party sources.

## What We Use Your Information For

We may use the information we collect from and about you for any of the following purposes:

  * To respond to your inquiries, and contact and communicate with you when necessary;
  * To review the usage and operations of our Site, develop new products or services, and conduct analysis to enhance or improve our content, products, and services;
  * To provide you with customized content, targeted offers, and, via email, or across other websites, social media, or online services;
  * To contact you with information, newsletters and promotional materials from us or on behalf of our partners and affiliates;
  * To use your data in an aggregated non-specific format for analytical and demographic purposes;
  * To address problems with the Site or our business, and to protect the security or integrity of the Site and our business;
  * For other purposes disclosed at the time you provide your information or otherwise with your consent.

Additionally, if you use the Site to connect with third-party services you authorize us to use information from and about you, on your behalf, to interact with these third-party services based on your requests.

## Information That We Share

We may share the information we collect from and about you in the following ways:

  *  **Affiliates** : We may share your information with our affiliates and subsidiaries for business, operational, promotional and marketing purposes.
  *  **Service Providers** : We may share your information with third party service providers that provide business, professional or technical support functions for us, help us operate our business and the Site, or administer activities on our behalf.
  *  **Sweepstakes, Contests, and Promotions:** If you choose to enter into one of our sweepstakes, contests, or other promotions (a “Promotion”) we may disclose your information to third parties or the public in connection with the administration of such Promotion, as required by law, as otherwise permitted by the Promotion’s official rules, or otherwise in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.
  *  **Other Third Parties** : We may share your information with our select partners, affiliates, and other third parties that we believe may have offers of interest to you.
  *  **Legal Matters And Safety** : We may access and disclose your information to respond to subpoenas, judicial processes, or government requests and investigations, or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law, or otherwise as required by law. We may disclose your information to protect the security of our Site, servers, network systems, and databases. We also may disclose your information as necessary, if we believe that there has been a violation of our Terms of Use, any other legal document or contract related to our services, or the rights of any third party.
  *  **Sale or Transfer of Business or Assets** : We may sell or purchase assets during the normal course of our business. If another entity acquires us or any of our assets, the information we have collected about you may be transferred to such entity.  In addition, if any bankruptcy or reorganization proceeding is brought by or against us, such information may be considered an asset of ours and may be sold or transferred to third parties.  Should such a sale or transfer occur, we will use reasonable efforts to try to require that the transferee use personal information provided through this Site in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy.
  *  **Aggregate or Anonymous Non-Personal Information** : We may also share aggregate or anonymous non-personal information with third parties for their marketing or analytics uses.
  *  **Other** : We also may share your information as disclosed to you at the time of collection.

### Your Choices And Opt-outs

 **Cookies, Tracking Options, and California Do Not Track Disclosures**

Certain parts of our Site require cookies. You are free to set your browser or operating system settings to limit certain tracking or to decline cookies, but by doing so, you may not be able to use certain features on the Site or take full advantage of all of our offerings. Please refer to your Web browser’s or operating system’s website or “Help” section for more information on how to delete and/or disable your browser or operating system from receiving cookies or controlling your tracking preferences.

Our system may not respond to Do Not Track requests or headers from some or all browsers. We may use cookies or other technologies to deliver more relevant advertising and to link data collected across other computers or devices that you may use.  To understand your choices for receiving more relevant advertising or to manage your settings, please review the information below:

  * To learn more about the use of cookies or other technologies to deliver more relevant advertising and to know your choices with respect to collection and use of the data by these third-party tools, you may visit the Digital Advertising Alliance’s (DAA) opt-out page at [http://www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/).
  * If you wish to prevent your data from being used by Google Analytics, Google has developed the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on available [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).
  * On your mobile device, you may also adjust your privacy and advertising settings to control whether you want to receive more relevant advertising.

 **Opt-Out Preferences**

We provide our customers with the opportunity to update their information or opt-out of having their information used for purposes not directly related to placement, processing, fulfillment, or delivery of a product order or servicing of your product. To opt-out of marketing communications, you may:

  * Send us an e-mail at contact@displayninja.com.
  * Contact us via our contact form in the”Contact” page, or
  * Unsubscribe from our email communications at any time by unsubscribing or following the instructions contained within the email.

If you receive marketing communications from one or more of our affiliates, you must opt-out individually from each of the affiliates from which you are receiving brand-specific marketing communications.

## Your California Privacy Rights

If you are a California resident, you may opt-out of our disclosure of personal information to third parties affiliated companies for their direct marketing purposes.  To opt out, please contact us at contact@displayninja.com.  You must put the statement “Your California Privacy Rights” in the subject field. We are not responsible for notices that are not labeled or sent properly, or do not have complete information.

Non-affiliated third parties are independent from Flexter ApS and if you wish to receive information about your disclosure choices or stop communications from such third parties, you will need to contact those non-affiliated third parties directly.

### Third-party Content, Links, and Plugins

The Site may have links to third-party websites, which may have privacy policies that differ from our own.  We are not responsible for the practices of such sites.

The Site may also offer you the ability to interact with social plugins from social media sites, which may allow us and/or the social media site to receive data from or about you. In some cases, we may know that you clicked on a social plugin, such as a Twitter Follow button, or receive other information from the social media sites. Similarly, if you have previously provided personal information to a third-party operating a plug-in on this Site, then such third-party may recognize you on this Site. Your use of social network plugins is subject to each social media site’s privacy policy, which may be different from ours, so please read these policies carefully to understand their policies and your options. As with linked sites, we have no control over the information that is collected, stored, or used by social network plugins, and are not responsible for the practices of such sites.

## Public Forums

Any information you may disclose on our Site, in blogs, on message boards, in chat rooms, or on other public areas on the Site or other third-party websites that this Site may link to, becomes public information.  Please exercise caution when disclosing personal information in these public areas.

## Children’s Privacy

Protecting children’s privacy is important to us. We do not direct the Site to, nor do we knowingly collect any personal information from, children under the age of thirteen.  If we learn that a child under the age of thirteen has provided personally identifiable information to the Site, we will use reasonable efforts to remove such information from our files.

## Data Security

We have taken certain physical, administrative, and technical steps to safeguard the information we collect from and about our customers and Site visitors. While we make every effort to help ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee our security measures.

## Data Storage

Your personal information may be stored on servers in the United States and is subject to the laws of the United States, where the data protection and other laws may differ from those of other countries. Your personal information may be disclosed in response to inquiries or requests from government authorities or to respond to judicial process in the countries in which we operate.

## Revisions To This Privacy Policy

We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change, modify, add, remove, or otherwise revise portions of this Privacy Policy at any time. When we do, we will post the change(s) on the Site and update the date at the top of this Privacy Policy.  Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to these terms means you accept these changes.  If we change the Privacy Policy in a material way, we will provide appropriate notice to you.

## How To Get In Touch With Us

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or the practices described herein, you may contact us at contact@displayninja.com or by mail to:

Flexter ApS  
Østerbro 37E, 1 TV  
9000 Aalborg  
Denmark  
Attention: Privacy

We use cookies to optimize site functionality and give you the best possible experience. Learn More
